[
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "안녕?",
            "response": "반가워요"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "이름이 뭐에요?",
            "response": "제 이름은 전준 이에요"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py",
            "response": "헬로우"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "하이",
            "response": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "안녕?",
            "response": "안녕 ㅎㅎ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "반가워",
            "response": "반갑지않아"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py",
            "response": "hi"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "hello",
            "response": "hi?"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "helloe?",
            "response": "nice to meet you"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py",
            "response": "됏나?"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "모르겠는데",
            "response": "왜 안되지?"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㄴㅇ",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㄴㅇ",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅇㄴ",
            "response": "ㅁ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅇㄴㅁ",
            "response": "아야"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "니이",
            "response": "가"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇㅁ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅇㄴㅁㅇㅁ",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇㅁㄴㅇㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㅇㄴㅇㅁㄴㅇ",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅇㄴㅁㅇ",
            "response": "ㅇㄴㅁㅇㄴ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㄴㅇ",
            "response": "ㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "",
            "response": "ㅁㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㄴㅇ",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㄴㅇ",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁ",
            "response": "ㅁㄴ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅇ& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㄴㅇㅁㄴㅇ",
            "response": "ㅇㄴㄴㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "왜",
            "response": "안돼"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "시@빨 짜증나네 슬슬",
            "response": "ㅋㅋ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py",
            "response": "일이삼사"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "오육칠팔",
            "response": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "& E:/python.exe e:/prj/ConnectionGpt/jsonRe.py",
            "response": "ㅁㄴㅇㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㄴㅇㅁㄴ",
            "response": "ㅇㅁㄴㅇ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㄴㅇ",
            "response": "ㅁ"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "ㅁㄴ",
            "response": "close"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "아아",
            "response": "마이크테스트"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "원투원투",
            "response": "원투원투"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "안녕하세요?",
            "response": "반갑습니다"
        }
    },
    {
        "data": {
            "question": "마지막",
            "response": "데이터"
        }
    }
]